So, someone had sent me a really ridiculous message, and I wasn't going to respond to it.
I wasn't even going to read it.
But then I realized, I've got time.
And I decided to use the nonsense as a learning exercise.
So, let's get into it.
This is Raven Lynn 1988, who says,
I don't care about what's going on in Israel right now.
I'm so incredibly worried about black people in the U.S.
We are in dangerous times.
My concern is my own country.
That is it.
To which I replied, this is dumb.
Now, some of you might say, Amanda, that was really harsh.
It's not that it's harsh as much as it is direct.
Because it is dumb.
It is choosing to be willfully ignorant.
To not want to know about what is going on in a country that is a proxy and a colonial extension of this country.
And I'm going to read to you her response and explain to you, through her response, the ways in which Israel actually does affect her.
Her response begins,
So, yes, I am a foundational black American.
So, we can just get that out the way.
Are you an FBA having to deal with everyday racial discrimination in the workplace, resulting in deteriorating mental health?
Well, interestingly enough, in Israel, they have universal health care that is funded largely in part or partially in part by our tax dollars.
So, the money that you are paying in taxes that actually goes to the federal government that they then make a choice on how to allocate is actually being used in part to send money to Israel to fund their health system where they actually do get support for mental health.
So, addressing the racial discrimination, Israel is founded by Zionists.
Zionists are racist.
Zionists are completely embedded and intricately involved in the way that our government operates here in the United States.
Thus, that means that they are supporting the racism that is happening legislatively at a rapid pace in this nation.
I'll continue.
Are you an FBA who has been fired six times in the last several years unjustly, causing you to lose out on thousands of dollars needed for mortgage, car payments, and college loan payments?
So, I will say that I don't know, actually, if you were fired unjustly.
But if I'm taking your word for it, what I can tell you is that, again, the money that you are losing out on and that you are paying in all of these disparate places, it should not be happening.
This is not a nation that should require you to worry about having a house over your head or having all of these student loan payments because in Israel, they actually have free college and they are paid to move to Israel.
They are literally given housing.
So, when you are talking about these hardships that you're having, while another country is not only not having those hardships, but is actually creating those hardships here, because I will expound upon that, it's important to acknowledge it.
So, for instance, right now, there are laws in Texas, Florida, and some other places, some other states, where you as a company cannot get any support from FEMA if you are boycotting Israel.
They are also about to pass on, they're about to pass a law, or they're working on passing a law that says, if you boycott Israel, or if you say anything against Israel, that you can have your passport revoked.
You literally can have your passport revoked.
And we also know that there are, oh, there's somebody in here talking crazy?
Hold on, let me block them.
907 Amulet Wears.
That sounds like a hotel.
Ooh, child, not 907 Amulet Wears.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha
that have said anything about Israel from getting any federal funding. We also need to acknowledge
that they are creating laws. For instance, in Texas, they are trying to charge two individuals
in Texas with felony counts for graffiti for saying, you know, free Palestine on a wall.
I will also add that because the United States is a part of an allyship with NATO,
with the United Nations and monetarily in the regard of how our dollar is the bottom line for
the world. We have to care about other countries because when other countries collapse, it leads
to the possibility that our country monetarily will collapse. Okay, let's continue. She says,
are you an FBA who is suffering from Trump's horrific? This sounds like a commercial for
a medication. Are you an FBA who's suffering from Trump's horrific economic policies, causing
inflation, making you panic every day about if you can afford gas, groceries, et cetera, for the next
six months and having to use credit for Uber Eats, groceries, et cetera? It is really unfortunate that
you are dealing with all of that. The same person that you are upset about is also not giving a damn
about those things while also providing dams for Israel. You should absolutely care that he is caring
more about and they are caring more about Israel. When you all say things like, I'm only worried about
black people while ignoring the fact that the people that you want to worry about you are actually
aiding others, you are actively not worried about black people because then you would say, hey, stop caring
about them and care about me. If you cannot, as a foundational black American, acknowledge that, then
where does your fight begin? Where does it begin? It's the same way that there were people who were like
mad that they were giving money and housing to immigrants. Why aren't you mad that they're not
giving money and housing to you? You're mad that they're giving, that's like being mad at the girl
cheating on your, cheating with fucking your man. You should be mad at your man. The girl came up.
You should be mad at your man. And by the way, that was a Trojan horse. Just so we're clear,
that was a Trojan horse. They actively brought those people in here. They actively brought those people in
here. So, like, next she goes on to say, are you an FBA who is currently in fear that civil rights
may be rolled back in the coming years and the current administration is laying the groundwork
as we speak? First of all, you should know that your civil rights have already been rolled back.
You should know that it is AIPAC and Zionist lobbies that have already infringed upon your civil rights.
They are already making decisions based. You already have representatives who are supposed
to be supporting you, representing you as the people making decisions based on the funding they
are getting from them. Namely, we can even just name two black representatives, Jamal Bowman and
Cori Bush, who were literally removed out of their positions in the Congress because there was so much
money funded from Israel to get people to run against them. So, when you're concerned about
the civil rights being rolled back, you should know that Israel is an integral part of your civil
rights being rolled back. Another one of your civil rights that's being rolled back is the right to
protest. When you saw college students and professors and administrators being attacked on campuses for
peacefully protesting the divestment of their tuition from Israel, you should have said this is deeply
concerning because if they're going to be attacking those people who are considered to be the privileged
over Israel, then that means I'm next. That means I'm next. So, when they are enacting violence against
people's First Amendment rights to protest, that is also your civil rights that are being
beat down. Speaking of beat down, you know where Derek Chauvin learned the knee hole that he did to
George Floyd that ultimately ended up in taking his life? From the Israeli offense forces because they
train our police officers. Yes. And the setup that they have over there to train their soldiers is what
they are looking to build all over this nation in cop cities. Urban warfare models, car driving models,
gun ranges, massive gun ranges. So, when you are saying that you're concerned about these things,
you need to know that these things are being perpetuated and refined in Israel against
Palestinians so that they can come and do it to you. Are you an FBA who is currently skeptical about
why the left-wing media is not doing anything about the rewriting of Charlie Kirk's legacy in the global
media and social media? Benjamin Netanyahu, who is the current prime minister or is the president,
I can never remember which one, of Israel, was one of the first to actually say, you know,
sending my condolences. So, in that, you know that he is then in cooperation with the U.S. government
because he is even just inserting himself into a conversation that has nothing to do with Israel, right?
In that regard, you have to know that the left-wing media is not a real thing. The media is owned by
oligarchs. It is also owned by Zionists. So, the media, the mainstream media is going to work
at the behest of the powers that be. And the powers that be have decided that eulogizing that individual
in this particular way, that creating a falsified framework around his existence and his death
is useful to them. So, therefore, you need to understand that that is in partnership with Israel.
She continues. She closes this by saying, what it, uh, media is not rewriting anything, uh,
seems like everyone except FBAs want C, because I refuse to say his name, to be remembered as a great
man who wasn't trying to ruin Black America. First of all, that is what I mean by being in a silo
and it being dumb to only care about your own people. You lose out on coalition. You actually
end up putting yourself through more stress because I can promise you there are far
than just foundational Black Americans who want to see this person properly contextualized in how
they lived their life as an ag, as an, as an aggressor and an agitator of violence.
It is imperative that we coalition build outside of our myopia, not just because it makes sense
logically, but also because it strengthens us. Okay. It strengthens us in so many ways. And I feel
like it's not really a clear, I feel like if it's not really a clear vision for you, then that means
that you need to expand your vision. Let's continue. What is dumb here is non FBA rich
celebrities who are not impacted by the majority of the things I just mentioned telling FBA women who
are impacted by all of these things that wanting to focus on their own lives in the States and not
a foreign war is dumb. It's not a foreign war. There are Americans who are literally over there right
now. There are Americans there in the context of soldiers. There are Americans there in the context of
a false fake organization that's supposed to be feeding Palestinians, but in actuality are allowing
them to be murked in the process of getting food. This is not a foreign war. It is also incredibly
reductive to think that any war is foreign. You think that because the war in the Congo is happening in
the Congo, that it's not affecting the world. You think that the war in Sudan is not affecting the
world. You're not a foundational black American. You're just a selfish person. Do not blame it on
your ancestry. Do not blame your inability to see beyond the context of your own existence as some
grounding in your awareness and protection of your people. You are a self-centered person.
And I promise you that a lot of the things that are happening in your life are government caused,
but could be community solved. So perhaps you need to get out of your own way because you should also
know that one, again, I am an FBA to this concept of rich. I find it fascinating because you want to be
rich. So somehow I am shaded for being able to actually get success out of my talent. This isn't
only fan success. And even that is like, go girl, get your thing. It's Ana's money. The inability to
think that I could, the inability to think I could have empathy for you is again, an example of your
limited scope. This is all projection. That's what this is. And the room that needs to be read is you
needing to read that the room is bigger than you. So to this person, uh, what's her name?
Raven Lynn, 1988. The world is bigger than you. The world is bigger than foundational black Americans.
Yep. The world is bigger than Americans. And the sooner that you understand that,
the better you will live because you will actually be able to see beyond your limitations that you've
created and understand how many more resources there actually are at your disposal and how many
connections there need to be made for you to prevent the same things that you're talking about
happening from continuing to happen. Adieu.